TINTU CHACKO

28B Freyberg Street, Waterloo, Lower Hutt, 5011.

Mobile: 02102745782

Email: tintuchacko2012@gmail.com

VISA STATUS – RESIDENT VISA

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/t1991/

Website: https://www.tintuchacko.com/

OBJECTIVE

To build a career in a leading corporate Hi-Tech environment with committed and dedicated people, which will help me to explore my abilities fully and realize my potential. Willing to work as a key player in a challenging and creative environment.

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am an energetic, ambitious person who has developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake, or situation that I am presented with. As a postgraduate with two years of experience in PHP programming, I am excellent at working with others to achieve a certain objective on time and with excellence. I consider myself to be hardworking and enjoy learning.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web Designing and : HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, ES6, React,

Programming PHP, SQL, jQuery, AJAX, WAMP, XAMPP, OOPs.

Database : MySQL , SQL Server.

Framework : PHP Codeigniter

Tools : Git & GitHub, Sublime Text, Visual studio Code,

Microsoft Office suite(Word, Excel, PowerPoint).

GitHub: https://github.com/tintuchacko

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Positive attitude.
- Work well in a team.
- Conscientious and determined to achieve goals.
- Responsible.
- · Quick learner.
- Can research and work independently.

WORK HISTORY

Oges Infotech

Kerala, India June 2015 – Sep 2017

Technolodge

Kerala, India Dec 2014 – May 2015

PHP Programmer

 Database Designing, developing, perform integration tests, client deployment, collect and make changes according to client feedback, etc.

PHP Developer (Codeigniter) Trainee

 Got experience in Database Designing, Website Designing, and development using Codeigniter framework and testing.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Udemy.com

July 2022 - Present

The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp

 A Full-Stack Web Development course(65+ hours). HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node, React, MongoDB, Web3 and DApps

QUALIFICATIONS

Mar Athanasius College

Kerala, India 2011 – 2014 **Master of Computer Applications (MCA)**

Indira Gandhi College of Arts and Science

Kerala, India 2008 – 2011 **BSc. Computer Science**

REFERENCES

Jithin Jose

Project Manager OGES iNFOTECH +91 9061672364 jithin@ogesinfotech.com

Harikrishnan C Nair

Team Leader OGES iNFOTECH +91 9633739303 hari@ogesinfotech.com